AMANDA ORDOÑEZ

WEB DEVELOPER

In my career as a researcher, I self learned how to program.

My background as a scientist gives me experience in analytical thinking, problem solving and teamwork in international projects. I combine these knowledges into Full Stack web development to use the best practices.

You can see more on <u>my portfolio</u>.

LANGUAGES

- Spanish: Native Proficiency
- English: Professional Working Proficiency

CONTACT INFORMATION

- 677 17 90 89, San Sebastián de los Reyes, Madrid
- amanda.daocegmail.com
- in Amanda Ordóñez Cencerrado
- Amanda-OC8

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

IRON HACK MADRID (08/2020-10/2020)

Master's degree in Geophysics

UNIVERSIDAD COMPLUTENSE DE MADRID (2014-2015)

Final Master Thesis: <u>Uso de georadar en el estudio de un yacimiento arqueológico</u>

Bachelor's degree in Physics

UNIVERSIDAD COMPLUTENSE DE MADRID (2007-2014)

SCIENTIFIC PUBLICATIONS

Díaz-Michelena, M. et al. The formation of a giant collapse caprock sinkhole on the Barda Negra plateau basalts (Argentina): Magnetic, mineralogical and morphostructural evidences. Geomorphology 367 (2020)

Magnetic characterization in the INTA Magnetism Laboratory. Ordóñez Cencerrado, A. A. et al. (2018) Oral Presentation, NEWTON Workshop

Improved understanding of magnetic signatures of basaltic lava flows and cones with implication for extraterrestrial exploration. Ordóñez Cencerrado, A. A., et al. (2017)

Poster, European Geosciencie Union (EGU17)

High resolution tracing of ore mineralization in the Río Odiel and Río Tinto region (Spain) using NEWTON magnetic instrument, Ordóñez Cencerrado A. A. et al. (2019) Poster, European Geosciencie Union (EGU19)



SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript ES6
- Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, React.js, Gatsby, Angular
- Git and GitHub control version, rest APIs
- MATLAB, Maxwell Ansys, VSM, magnetic characterization

WORK EXPERIENCE

Superior Technician

INSTITUTO NACIONAL DE TÉCNICA AEROESPACIAL (11/2017-01/2020)

- Magnetic characterization of natural and artificial samples using VSM
- Development a novel instrument for magnetic susceptibility characterization
- Magnetic simulation
- MATLAB software development

Formation Student

INSTITUTO NACIONAL DE TÉCNICA AEROESPACIAL (10/2015-11/2017)

- Magnetic simulation
- Magnetic characterization of natural samples
- Magnetic mapping
- Learning about the magnetic instrumentation

Internship Student

GEOFÍSICA APLICADA CONSULTORES (11/2014-01/2015)

- Analysis of GPR 3D on an engineering civil project
- Development MATLAB software for processing and representation

PROJECTS

Kraken World Studios (10/2020-10/2020)

- An online workspace for writers and worldbuilders to plan novels, shorts stories, comic scripts...
- Technologies: JavaScript ES6, React.js, MongoDB

Monumentos activos (09/2020-09/2020)

- App to do activities in different monuments along the city of Madrid
- Technologies: Handlebars, JavaScript ES6, Node.js, MongoDB, Google maps API

Why did the chicken cross the road? (09/2020-09/2020)

- A Frogger-like videogame. Avoid obstacles in two dimensions. Local multiplayer
- Technologies: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript ES6, Canvas